Everyone in our class...
had been talking about Yuuki who had recently transferred in.
Wow!
Coming, coming.
Please step out, Miss.
Miss, here is your bag.
Miss, your indoor shoes.
Have a good day!
Hey, Yuuki-san. What should I call you?
Yuuki-san? Or Nona-chan?
You just transferred so if you have any questions, please don't hesitate to ask.
Anything about club activities...
Or the rank of the teacher's popularity.
Please excuse me.
I am currently studying a very significant theorem right now.
Wow!
Cool!
Amazing!
Haru is like a completely different person when he's in the water.
Although he usually just dazes around.
Tsuwabuki-kun...
Okay!
Instead of the PE teacher, who's currently on break, I'll be in charge of the class.
Wow, that was an excellent time there.
In fact, it's the best.
So... why isn't Yuuki-san swimming?
Why read when you can swim?
Maybe she can't swim...
Akihime-san, it's your turn next.
Sensei, Sumomo can't really swim.
Ah, Tsuwabuki-kun, please help teach Akihime-san how to swim.
Huh? Me?
Why?
You're both in the Gardening Club, right?
So you can help her with some special training.
Special training?!
Hey, how about you, Yuuki-san?
If you are bad with water, why don't you take the special training with Sumomo-chan?
I don't have anything that I'm bad at though.
There is no such thing as being bad with water.
Amazing, Yuuki-san.
So she's good in athletics too.
Good style and body!
All the guys will go head over heels.
Amazing!
Miss.
S-Sorry.
It's okay...
I'm really sorry.
Hey Haru, why are you blushing?
N-No way.
I'm not blushing!
You're blushing. You...
Ugh! It's hot and humid!
Why is it so hot and humid for dolls?
Why don't I have the courage...?
I'm bad with water.
Maybe it's because of all the things that happened when I was little.
Doggy, doggy!
Fishy, fishy!
I can't even put my face inside the pool.
Don't worry about things like that!
The star drop!
Nako-chan.
I saw the light, so...
There it is!
It's inside the pool.
What is this?
Why is it so deep?
I can't see anything.
Sumomo, are you alright?
Y-Yes.
You don't have to do this...
I'm fine. I'll try...
W-What?!
Nako-chan!
You look pathetic, Prima Plam.
Who is she?
Umm... Aspalas-san?
No! I am Prima Aspalas, which means I'm Saint Aspalas' Prima.
Saint Aspalas?
So it's Aspalas-san, huh?
Nice to meet you.
So you've come to interfere with Sumomo again?
Interfere? That's outrageous!
I'm here to give you my guidance!
G-Guidance?
I want to have a fair fight with you.
That's why I want you to become stronger.
Listen and watch carefully.
When the star drop is underwater, this magic will be the most effective.
Rimu Comiti Aqua!
W-What is that, Aspalas-san?
Arthur.
R-Right away, Miss.
This is a spell that repels water.
With this, you can't get wet and you can breathe underwater.
So if I chant those words...
You can go underwater and capture the star drop.
However, a person who is scared of water will be unable to use this magic.
Are you surprised?
Don't tell me you're afraid of water?
Miss.
So you really are afraid of water.
Yuuki-san, how good are your eyes?
Or does it improve when you're in those clothes?
Did you just call me Yuuki?
Well, those are Yuuki-san's glasses.
Yuuki-san is Aspalas-san?!
Listen, there is another world which coexists with our own.
In that world Figurare, there are two academies.
The academies' names are Plam Cloris and Saint Aspalas.
Both academies train Stellar Spinears to gather the star drops.
Every year, the choosing of each academies' best student as their representative...
and sending them to this world to compete for the star drops has become a tradition.
Competition for the star drops?
It was meant to help improve both academies.
And whoever manages to gather all seven star drops will be declared the winner.
So that means...
I am Saint Aspalas' representative, Prima Aspalas.
Miss is such an excellent student that many predict that Saint Aspalas will surely win this year.
But, then... what happened to the other academy's representative?
Ah, that girl came here once but had to go back due to sudden illness.
That's why another representative was chosen.
You're talking about me?!
Right. The ring chose you.
Mysteriously, the ring chose a normal girl who doesn't know anything about the star drops.
So in other words, Sumomo is already participating in the two academies' competition?
That's basically what it's become.
Incidentally, it just so happened that there was someone who needed the star drops as well.
Incidentally, huh?!
You will need all seven star drops to save him too.
I won't approve of this!
Academy student or not, anyone can chant first rate magic.
You probably can't even do that!
I will never approve of competing with someone like that.
Rimu Comiti Aqua...
The magic spell that repels water should not be in your Recipe.
Why? Because you're afraid of water!
Come with me!
What are you doing?! Come on!
Sensei...
It's alright.
She is Saint Aspalas' representative who holds high standards.
She won't hurt people randomly.
Okay.
A Stellar Spinear who is afraid of water will never make any progress.
Pramu Victor!
Oh, that is excellent, Miss.
You have twenty-four hours left.
After that, the star drop will be sealed inside the pool.
Try and capture the star drop within that time.
If you can't then you'll never be able to gather all seven star drops, Prima Plam.
Aradi Fumei!
Sumomo...
I have to gather the star drops...
I have to gather all seven of them!
Otherwise, Yuki-chan won't be able to go home.
I can't keep on always being afraid of water.
I shouldn't disappoint Yuuki.
Now, in the beginning you should use a kickboard.
Yes!
Just relax.
Now, try lifting your feet off of the floor.
Slowly move your body forward.
Sumomo!
A-Are you alright?
Relax and breathe.
Hey, you don't have to force yourself.
It's alright.
One more time, please!
This is the first time I've seen Akihime with this expression.
I'm alright.
Sumomo.
I'm alright, really.
Akihime...
Do your best!
Do your best, Akihime!
You did your best, until your body felt this cold.
There's no need to hurry.
It will be fine. You will overcome your fear in no time.
Because...
I think that Akihime really... is very courageous.
Later.
Tsuwabuki-kun!
Today... Today... T-Thank...
I-I'm sorry! I'll see you later!
Sumomo!
Sorry... Yuki-chan.
I'm sorry...
It's alright. If you can't do it today, in time you will.
Even with the gathering of the the star drops too...
Yuki-chan.
Because Yuki-chan came to me, many great things have happened.
And I... And I...
I think that Akihime really... is very courageous.
Thank you, Tsuwabuki-kun.
Watch me, Yuki-chan.
Ruuche Ruvi Avis
The characters!
Err... Rimu...
Rimu Comiti Aqua!
Nako-chan!
I'm going.
I can really breathe!
Yeah.
And I can move freely too.
It's like flying.
This is amazing, Sumomo!
Let's try this!
It seems bottomless, but...
There it is!
Sumomo.
Yup.
Puruvu Radi!
That girl...
A chant she heard only once; she mastered it on her first attempt.
Even for a student in the academy, it takes at least a week to do that.
Also, using it at that level...
I had doubts about Arthur's report, but...
The shy and timid Akihime successfully overcame her fear of water.
That alone took a lot of courage.
While being together with her as Yuki-chan,
I felt something changing inside of me along with her.
And... I started to become confused.
The summer season fun!
Making curry!
Test of courage!
Hot spring!
Pillow fight!
And also,
Confessing to someone you like at night!
Who, who is it?
Who do you like?
Umm...
Boys are not allowed to enter!